# VERONIKA HARBACHOVA

Austin, TX 78701 | 734.834.2893 | veronika.har@hotmail.com

# **Profile Summary**

Linguist turned web developer blends soft skills of adaptability and openmindedness with hard skills of web development. Cross-functional collaboration with tech teams and successful experience of working as a part of one. Have developed a flexible, empathetic communication style that serves as a compliment to the technical rigor required to excel as a coder. Experienced multi-lingual and cross-cultural project manager that listens first and enjoys translating business requirements into technical capabilities.

## Experience

PNI Media – Austin, TX, USA

Frontend Developer | 02/2020 – now Tech stack: React, Sass, Typescript

## **Freelance Web Developer** - 12/2018 - 02/2020

- ✓ Portfolio website: <a href="https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com/">https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com/</a>;
- ✓ Github account: <a href="https://github.com/VeronikaHar">https://github.com/VeronikaHar</a>;
- ✓ 10+ projects using React, Node, Vue, Angular etc. Currently working on a collaboration project of a cross-platform archery mobile app;
- ✓ A project example: a movie web app that requires users to create an account to access information on movies, directors, genres, add/remove favorite movies to the profile, edit/delete their account info. The app uses RESTful API. Front-end done with React, Redux and Bootstrap. Back-end done with Node and MongoDB.

## **Generation\_P** – *Minsk, Belarus*

XSLT developer / Assistant Team-Leader | 09/2007 - 08/2008

- ✓ Achieved full technical competency in 3 months without any prior experience (CVS repo; PAROS (POST/GET); Oxygen+Eclipse; XML etc);
- ✓ Assistant Team-Leader supervised team performing patch-and-release responsibilities and negotiated business solutions with foreign customers.

#### Education

#### **Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development**

CareerFoundry | 01/2019 - 11/2019

- 300+ hours of training/mentoring with industry leading Front-End and Senior Full-Stack Web Developer.
- Intensive project-based training program with a focus on JavaScript, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools;

## **Master of Arts in Linguistics**

Dalian University of Technology | 09/2008 - 07/2011

### **Bachelor of Arts in Linguistics**

Belarusian State University | 09/2003 - 06/2008

### Skills

React.js

Redux

**React Native** 

Node.js

jQuery

JavaScript

**REST API** 

HTML/HTML5

CSS/CSS3

**PWA** 

**Bootstrap** 

**Responsive Design** 

**TDD** 

## **Toolkit**

NPM

TypeScript

Sass

Jest / Enzyme

MongoDB

Heroku

CodePen

Git / GitHub

**Google Analytics** 

Google Tag Manager

**Chrome Dev Tools** 

Photoshop